http://www.smbb.com/privacy-policy

Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky understands that your privacy is important. Therefore, please carefully review our Privacy Policy, which explains what data we collect regarding you and how that data is used. Since all computers connected to the Internet are given a domain name and an Internet Protocol (IP) address, when you visit an Internet Web site, you disclose your IP address, the time of your visit, and the referring location (the site or page that offered a link to the smbb.com page). This information is used by us for system administration and other business related purposes. When you visit our web site (“Site”) we may collect click-stream data (such as information as the page requested, the source of the request, the preceding page viewed, and the type of browser making the request) for marketing and system administration purposes.
Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky also collects personal data (such as your name, occupation, mailing address, e-mail address and telephone number) about you that you provide to us voluntarily, such as through our online contact form. We use personal data for a variety of business reasons, including contacting you, providing services, developing new services, and for our planning, marketing and strategic information purposes. Personal data may be disclosed as necessary to third parties in the following circumstances: (i) where the third party is under contract with us to improve and provide services associated with the Site; (ii) where we believe, in our sole discretion, that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky, its users, or the general public;  (iii) in order to investigate, prevent or take legal action against suspected fraud or other illegal activities; and (iv) when Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky enters, or may reasonably enter, into a corporate transaction, such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, asset purchase, or a financing transaction. Finally, if Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky becomes involved in a bankruptcy or insolvency, the database containing personal data may be treated as an asset of Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky.
In order to provide a customized, personal service, Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky may use cookies to store and help track your information. Internet “cookies” save data about individual users, so that when you revisit the Site, Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky may recognize you by the Internet cookie and customize your experience accordingly. You may decline any Internet cookies by using the appropriate feature of your Web client software, if available. Finally, Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky collects aggregate and user-specific statistical information to calculate overall usage statistics.
The confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky via this Site or e-mail cannot be guaranteed. Accordingly Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet. For a more private communication, you can contact Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky by telephone at 1-215-496-8282.
As a convenience to our users, this Site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the content and privacy policy of these linked sites. You should review the privacy practices and policies of these other web sites.
We do not disclose our clients’ Personally Identifiable Information to unaffiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes. Except as necessary for Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky to provide the services requested by you, you may opt out of having your personal information used by Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky and for disclosure to third parties by contacting Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky via email at the following address: info@smbb.com. In addition, you may review and update the personal information that we have regarding you by contacting us at info@smbb.com or by mailing to: Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky, One Liberty Place, 52nd Floor, 1650 Market Street, Philadelphia, PA 19103.
Saltz Mongeluzzi & Bendesky reserves the rights to change this Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice to you. The date the Privacy Policy was last changed is provided below for your convenience. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy for changes, and your continued use of this Site after any changes made to this Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes.
This Policy was last updated on August 19, 2011.
Ready for a free confidential case evaluation?
Contact us TODAY. Timing is critical for your case.
Call 215.496.8282
or
Fill out the contact form
Browse by Last Name:
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ
Search for:
Search
Clear All Filters
Ara R. AvrigianBenjamin J. BaerElizabeth A. BaileyCarmen P. BelefonteLarry BendeskyMarni S. BergerRobert N. BrakerMichael A. BudnerDaniel L. CeislerJoshua C. CohanLawrence R. CohanE. Douglas DiSandro, Jr.Samuel B. DordickAndrew R. DuffyKristen M. Gibbons FedenScott A. FellmethMary T. GidaroJeffrey P. GoodmanMatthew A. GrubmanK. Andrew HeinoldPatrick HowardJordan HowellGregory R. KissDavid L. KwassDavid J. LangsamKeith P. MeccaRobert J. MongeluzziAdam J. PantanoSimon B. ParisTracy D. SchwartzJ. Peter VeloskiJason S. WeissSteven G. WigrizerRobert W. Zimmerman
Aerial Lift/Scissor Lift AccidentsAFFF InjuriesAmputationsAsbestos/Mesothelioma InjuriesBenzene InjuryBirth InjuriesBoating and Maritime InjuriesBrain InjuriesBurn InjuriesCivil RightsClaims Against Alcohol ServersClass ActionsConstruction Accident & Injury AttorneysConstruction FallsCrane Accidents and Tip-OversDangerous Baby and Children’s ProductsDefective Automobiles and TiresDrowning AccidentsElectrical InjuriesFalse Claims Act/Qui TamForklift AccidentsFraternity HazingIndustrial AccidentsInsurance and Bad Faith ClaimsMedical MalpracticeMotorcycle AccidentsNegligent SecurityNursing Home NegligencePremises LiabilityProducts LiabilityRoadside AccidentsRoof AccidentsScaffold AccidentsSexual AbuseSpinal Cord InjuriesSports and Recreational InjuriesStructural CollapsesTrain AccidentsTrucking AccidentsVaccine InjuryVehicle AccidentsVictims of CrimesWorkplace AccidentsWrongful Death
Search for:
Search
